Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.06.20 15:42:40
在布鲁克林成长的我
Growing up in Brooklyn,
一直以为去远方旅行...
I always thought that traveling to faraway places was something
只能是有钱人的消遣
that only rich people did.
都13岁 俺还没出过纽约州
At 13, I'd never been out of New York,
但情况即将改变
but all that was about to change.
同学们 我要宣布一件事
Class, I have an announcement.
我们要到华盛顿特区来一场实地考察旅行
We're all going on a field trip to Washington, DC.
你们只需让父母在许可卡上签个字
You just need to have your parents sign your permission slips
并要卖30盒饼干来补充旅行费用
and sell 30 boxes of cookies to cover the cost of the trip.
Chris
Chris.
如果你家付不起现金
If your people can't afford to pay cash,
我可以考虑收取粮票
I'll see if we'll accept food stamps.
她当这是鱼子酱啊
She acts like it's caviar.
这只是饼干 该死的
It's just cookies, damn.
我们怎么去?
How are we going to get there?
我们租了一辆公车
We're chartering a bus.
准备坐最后吧 乡巴佬
Prepare to sit in the back, Birmingham.
我倒希望你坐公车下面
I'd like to sit you under a bus.
1x21 Everybody Hates Dreamgirls.
Transcript: Raceman Adaptation: Sixe
人人都恨克里斯 第1季 第21集 "人人都恨进监狱"
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
这是什么?
What's this?
宝贝 你用不着给我买东西!
Oh, baby, you didn't have to get me anything!
没错 他以前是没买
Oh, yes, he did.
不过他可是吃一堑 长一智
My father learned that the hard way.
是你说的不用给你买东西啊!
You're the one that told me not to get you nothing!
捅俺干啥?!
What you stab me for?!
Rochelle!
那天不过是植树节
And it was just Arbor Day.
Rochelle!
赶快打开吧
Go ahead, open it.
看看你给了我什么...
Let's see what you got me.
这太甜蜜了 宝贝
This is so sweet, baby.
梦女郎!
Dreamgirls!
天啊 梦女郎!
Oh, Dreamgirls!
宝贝!
Oh, baby!
你怎么弄到的梦女郎演唱会门票的?
How did you get tickets to Dreamgirls?
多贵啊
These are expensive.
价格还好 我从Risky那买的
It's okay, I got them from Risky.
Risky?
爸爸以前从Risky那买过票--
My father has gotten tickets from Risky before--
是在麦迪逊花园上演的 阿里・弗雷泽对抗赛的票
for the Ali-Frazier fight at Madison Square Garden.
发生什么了?
What happened?
谁被击倒了? 怎么了?
Who's down? What happened?
真帅!
Man!
他还买过Patti LaBelle在 林肯中心演唱会的票
He got him tickets to see Patti LaBelle at Lincoln Center.
她穿的什么?
What's she wearing?
她扔鞋了吗?
Did she throw her shoe yet?
我接到Patti的鞋了!
I got Patti's shoe!
闻闻!
Smell it!
Patti 我爱你 甜心!
Yes, Patti, I love you, girl!
别担心好吗 我们会玩得开心的
Don't worry, we're gonna have a good time, okay?
会的! 我们会玩得开心的!
We are! We're gonna have a good time!
谢谢你 宝贝 你是这世界上最可爱的人
Thank you, baby. You are the sweetest man in the world.
Tonya 早餐!
Tonya, breakfast!
妈妈 我好像被什么给咬了
Mama, I think something bit me.
不 宝贝 这可能不是被什么给咬的
No, baby, I don't think these are bites.
你长水痘了
You've got chicken pox.
谁传的她?
Who gave her chicken pox?
不是我
Wasn't me.
要我拿点止咳糖浆吗?
Want me to get the Robitussin?
不用 止咳糖浆不管用
No, I don't think Robitussin's gonna help this.
听着 Chris Drew
Look, Chris and Drew,
我不想你们被传染 所以 离Tonya远点
I don't need y'all getting sick, so I need y'all to stay away from Tonya.
这听起来像让我们远离一个连环杀人
That's like saying stay away from a serial killer.
好的
Okay.
妈妈 你在许可卡上签字了吗
Mom. Did you sign my permission slip?
夹你书里了 宝贝
It's in your book, baby.
什么许可卡?
Permission for what?
去华盛顿特区野外郊游
A field trip to Washington, DC.
我得卖光饼干才能去
I need to sell cookies so I can go.
你能帮我卖一些吗?
Can you take a few boxes to work?
很抱歉 Chris
Oh, I'm sorry, Chris,
我不能再去卖东西了
but I can't ask these people to buy nothing else.
我帮你妈妈卖过雅芳化妆品
I've sold Avon for your mother,
帮Tonya卖过包装纸 帮Drew卖过巧克力条...
wrapping paper for Tonya, chocolate bars for Drew...
好吧
Okay.
别 别 别
No, no, no.
我要告诉你
I'll tell you what.
我要买两盒 让你开张
I'll buy two boxes for myself to get you started.
其他的 你要自己处理
The rest, you're gonna have to handle yourself.
谢谢你 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
Bed-Stuy至少住了10万人
With at least 100,000 people living in Bed-Stuy,
卖掉28盒饼干应该不是啥难事
selling 28 boxes of cookies couldn't be that hard.
有人在吗?
Hello?
她说她满18岁了!
She said she was 18!
嘿!
Hey!
你想买...
Would you like to buy...
别在意
Never mind.
想买饼干吗?
Would you like to buy some cookies?
我要四盒
I'll take four.
你在干什么?!
What are you doing?!
他有糖尿病
He has diabetes.
你想杀了他吗?
You trying to kill him?
难以想象卖个饼干比卖个毒品还麻烦
I can't believe it's harder selling cookies than crack.
妈妈告诉过我们离Tonya远点
My mother told us to stay away from Tonya,
但对Drew来说还是太迟了
but it was too late for Drew.
你这样会越来越严重 孩子
You're gonna make it worse, boy.
别抓了
Stop scratching.
为什么她不说别长头发了?
Why don't she just tell him to stop growing hair?
好痒
But it itches.
去坐那
Sit  over here.
妈妈 我屁股痒
Mama, my booty itches.
过来
Oh, come here.
让我看看
Let me see.
宝贝 你不能抓 轻轻拍拍
See,  baby, you can't scratch, you got to pat.
怎样? 是不是感觉好些?
See? Does that feel better?
嗯
Yes.
好了 回到床上去 好吗?
All right, go back to bed, okay?
让我看看
Let me see.
100度 不是很糟
Ooh, 100 degrees, that's not so bad.
躺这休息一会
Here, lay down, get some rest.
我过会再来看你
I'll come check on you later.
别抓了 你让我都痒了
And stop scratching. You're making me itch.
找到保姆了吗?
You find anyone?
没人想照看生水痘的孩子
Nobody wants to baby-sit kids with chicken pox.
那算了吧 梦女郎演唱会
Well, there goes Dreamgirls.
无论怎样 谢谢你 宝贝 你知道吗?
Thanks anyway, baby. You know what?
这是你给我的最好的礼物
This would have been the best present you ever gave me.
这可不是第一次 因为我们之中有人生病
It wouldn't be the first time my parents missed something
而耽误父母出行
because one of us was sick.
我拿到了免费用餐券!
I got a coupon for a free dinner!
我马上去打扮!
Oh, I'm gonna get dressed.
妈妈 我得了狂犬病
Mama, I have rabies!
该死!
Damn!
我拿到了Michael Jackson演唱会的票!
I got Michael Jackson tickets!
我给保姆打电话
Oh, I'll call the sitter.
妈妈 我眼球掉出来了
Mama, my eye fell out.
该死!
Damn!
我们赢了一次去迈阿密的旅行!
We just won a trip to Miami!
我马上收拾行李!
Ooh, I'm gonna go get packed!
妈妈 我脖子扭了
Ma, I think I broke my neck.
该死
Damn.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
别 Julius 没事的
Oh, no, Julius, it's okay.
我们只是 又在家过了一个结婚纪念日
We'll just spend another anniversary at home.
至少我们在一起
At least we'll be together.
你知道吗?
You know what?
这票很贵
These tickets are expensive.
我们不必都在家坐着
There's no reason why both of us should sit at home.
我来看孩子 你去看演唱会
I'll watch the kids. You go.
好的
Okay.
要是她怀里有个球 她肯定去纽卡斯尔联队打比赛了
If she had a ball, she could have played for the Jets.
Sheila!
我们可以去看梦女郎了!
We're going to see Dreamgirls!
没错
That's right.
当你想让女人拆穿你的谎言时 她们却从不那样做
Women never catch you in a lie when you want them to.
一会见
Okay.
*And I am telling you I'm not going*
And I am telling you I'm not going
*You're the best man I've ever known*
You're the best man I've ever known
*And there's no way I could ever ever go*
And there's no way I could ever, ever go
*Darling there's no way*
Darling, there's no way
*No...*
No...
*I'm living without ya*
I'm living without ya
*I'm not living without ya*
I'm not living without ya
*Not living without ya*
Not living without ya
*I don't want to be*
I don't want to be
*Free-e-e-e-e-e*
Free-e-e-e-e-e
*I'm staying*
I'm staying
*And you you you*
And you, you, you
*You're gonna love me...*
You're gonna love me...
Jennifer 我来了
Jennifer, I'm coming!
爸爸
Daddy,
能帮我抓抓屁股吗?
can you scratch my booty?
拜托
Please?
伙计 你得加把劲了
Dude, you got to pull it together.
这可是今年最棒的郊游了
This is the best field trip all year.
我可能会见到Tip O'Neill
I might get to see Tip O'Neill.
谁?
Who?
你没听说过Thomas Tip O'Neill?
You've never heard of Thomas Tip O'Neill?
除非他和大鲨鱼奥尼尔有关
Not unless he's related to Shaquille.
他是有史以来 众议院最著名发言人
He's only like the most famous Speaker of the House of Representatives ever.
我不知道还能做什么
Well, I don't know what else I can do.
我已经敲了快100扇门了
I knocked on, like, 100 doors.
你最好再敲100扇 小奥尼尔
Well, you better knock on 100 more, Jermaine,
如果我没在去往特区的公车上
'cause if I'm not on that bus to DC,
我就把你的脸揍开花
I'm gonna freedom march all over your face.
算上卖给我爸爸的那两盒饼干
Counting the two boxes of  cookies I had sold to my dad,
我一共才卖了两盒 还被偷了一盒
I had sold two boxes of cookies and had one stolen.
我得想个新点子
I needed a new strategy.
打扰下 想来盒饼干吗?
Excuse me. would you like to buy a box of cookies?
它们能喝吗?
Can I get drunk on those cookies?
嗨 Risky 想来盒饼干吗?
Hey, Risky, you want to buy a box of cookies?
嘿 小朋友 俺管卖不管买
Hey, youngblood, I don't buy, I sell.
想来个VCR吗?
You want to buy a VCR?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
嘿 要买VCR吗?
Hey. You need a VCR?
我已经有一个了
I got one already.
这可是今早从卡车上掉下来的
Fell off the truck this morning.
真的吗? 我来两个
Really? I'll take two.
真没想到这街区唯一能卖出去的
I never realized the only stuff that sold on the street
竟是偷来的东西
in my neighborhood was stolen stuff.
饼干!  卖饼干!
Cookies!  Cookies for sale!
巧克力曲奇 花生酱口味 巧克力人偶 薄荷巧克力口味
Chocolate chip, peanut butter, Do-Si-Do, chocolate mint!
我买完了
I got cookies.
这可是今早从卡车上掉下来的
They just fell off the truck this morning.
你怎么不早说?
Why didn't you say so?
我要两盒
Give me two boxes.
谢谢
Thank you.
我都等不及要回学校了
I couldn't wait to get back to school.
你就是卖饼干的那小子?
You the kid selling the cookies?
刚从卡车上掉下来的
Right off the truck.
你来几盒?
How  many you want?
一盒都不要
None.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
有关被捕 我只在电视上看到过
All I knew about getting arrested was what I saw on TV.
他们告诉你你的权力...
They read you your rights...
你有权保持缄默
You have the right to remain silent.
你可以打一个电话...
...and you get a phone call...
你可以打一个电话
You get one call.
伙食很差
and the food is horrible.
谢谢
Thanks.
我发现 被逮捕后最惨的就是...
What I found out was that the worst part of getting arrested
被当成犯人对待
is being treated like a criminal.
对不起 我能去下厕所吗?
Excuse me, can I use the bathroom?
你卖赃物之前应该考虑到
Should have thought about using the bathroom
去厕所的问题
before you started selling stolen goods.
我没卖赃物
I wasn't selling stolen goods.
那我们抓错人了?
Then we must have got the wrong guy.
我不能打个电话吗?
Don't I get, like, a phone call?
你卖赃物之前应该考虑到
Should have thought about making a phone call
打电话的问题
before you started selling stolen goods.
我知道我表面上看来很平静
I know I looked cool on the outside,
但我心里... 是这么想的...
but on the inside, I was doing this...
我再也不这么干了 我保证!
I won't do it anymore, I promise!
我不是小偷!
I'm not a thief!
我要见妈妈!
I want my mama!
我想了一个又一个
All I was thinking was one way or another,
希望能被放出去的办法
I wish they'd let me go.
而在家里... 爸爸也在考虑同样的事
Back at home, my father was thinking the same thing.
我看起来怎样?
How do I look?
你已经换了5次了
You changed five times already.
第一次就挺好了
You looked fine the first time.
谢谢 宝贝 我只是太激动了
Oh, thank you, baby. I'm just so excited.
我是说 要见梦女郎了
I mean, this is Dreamgirls.
梦女郎!
Dreamgirls!
这就像是终身不遇二次的事
This is like a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
正是一生难得的机会
It's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
- 是的 - 所以 你最好赶快出发
- Yeah. - So, uh, you better get going.
没错 宝贝
You're right, baby.
你对我太好了
Oh, you are so good to me.
梦女郎
D reamgirls.
*We'll make you happy*
We'll make you happy.
*Yeah yeah yeah*
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
爸爸 痒死我了
Daddy, I'm itchy!
过来 去站到那组人里
Come on, I need to put you in a lineup.
那组人?
A lineup?
没错 很明显 前几天在卑尔根东
Yeah, apparently a delivery truck carrying cookies
有辆运饼干的卡车被抢劫了
was hijacked in East Bergen the other day.
我猜你可能在想 谁会去拦一辆运饼干的卡车?
I know you're probably thinking who would hold up a cookie truck?
别动! 别动!
Don't move! Don't move!
把所有的饼干都交出来! 觉得我在开玩笑?
All we want are your cookies! Think I'm playing?
走啦!
Now, go!
- 我这么做不会被判刑的... - 快跑!
- I'm not doing time for this-- - Go!
我没抢劫卡车
I didn't hijack a truck.
我连卑尔根东在哪都不知道
I don't even know where East Bergen is.
你卖赃物之前应该考虑到这些问题
Should have thought of that before you started selling stolen cookies.
我不会在那里洗澡的 太恶心了
I ain't taking a bath in that. That looks nasty.
这样可以缓解瘙痒
It'll help your itching.
可是我不喜欢麦片
But I don't like oatmeal.
没让你吃它们 孩子 只是在那里洗澡
You don't have to eat it, girl, you got to take a bath in it.
然后她得把它们吃了
Then she's got to eat it.
我爸爸从不浪费食物
My father didn't waste food.
不是我偷的 我在Corleone中学读书
It wasn't me. I go to Corleone Junior High.
我从学校拿的饼干
I got the cookies from school,
我得把它们都卖了 才能去华盛顿特区野外郊游
and I'm just selling them so I can go on some trip to Washington, DC.
这不是偷来的
And I did not steal them.
我只有那么说 人们才会来买
I was just saying that so people would want to buy them.
你在Corleone上学?
You go to Corleone?
你是那唯一一个黑人孩子吧?
What are you the only black kid there?
不错的尝试
Nice try.
你符合那个目击证人的描述 饼干小子
There was an eyewitness, and you fit the profile, cookie boy.
即使只有13岁
I may have only been 13,
我已经明白什么是种族歧视了
but I already knew how racial profiling worked.
目击证人说...
This is what the witness said...
他是个黑人 男的
He was a black male,
普通肤色 大概6尺4寸 230磅
medium complexion, about 6'4, 230 pounds.
眼睛是褐色的
He had brown eyes.
他穿着小便装 带着黄色小便帽
Um, he was wearing a-- Scout uniform with a yellow beanie,
下身穿的深色短裤 穿了双14码的深色的鞋
and he had on dark pants, and size 14 dark shoes.
他左手腕背面有块胎记
And, uh, a birthmark on the back of his left wrist.
还有 他走路有点跛
Oh, and- and he walked with a limp.
但这些是警察听来的...
But this is what the cop heard...
他特征是黑的 黑黑的男人
Um, he was black, and, uh,
黑黑的肤色
black, black, and black.
黑黑的体型
Um, black, black,
黑黑的眼睛
and he black, black, black,
黑的外套 黑的帽子
black, black, black.
还有 他穿着黑黑的裤子和鞋...
And, uh, he had, uh,
胎记也黑的
black, black, black, black.
都是黑的
And, oh, a black.
没错 还有 他和一个黑人在一起
Yeah. And, uh, he walked with a black.
脸朝前
Face forward.
2号 站好!
Number two, stand still!
看起来就像Commodores最新专辑的封面
That looks like the cover of the last Commodores album.
通常 爸爸会盼着妈妈高兴
Usually, my father wanted my mother to be happy.
但这次 他偷偷祈祷
But this was the one time he was secretly hoping
Risky给他的票 能像往常一样烂
that the tickets that Risky gave him were horrible as usual.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
这座位棒极了!
These seats are great!
- 没错! - 亲爱的 虽然我不想这么说
- I know! - Oh, girl, I hate to say it,
但你的孩子长水痘了 真是太好了
but I'm glad your kids got the chicken pox. Oh!
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
谢谢
Oh, thank you,
我们爱你!
We love you!
别走! 继续!
Don't go! You stay!
你最好不要走!
You better go, girl!
*我会留下来!*
I'm staying!
嘿
Hey.
Chris回来了吗?
Is Chris here yet?
没有 我猜他还在外面卖饼干
No, I guess he's still out selling cookies.
好的
Okay.
嘿 爸爸 能给我腋窝上点药吗
Hey, dad? Can you get my armpit?
那么...妈妈什么时候回来?
So, uh, when's mom coming home?
得再过一会
It'll be a while.
她还拿走了我的优惠卷 和Sheila一起去吃晚餐了
She's using my coupon to take Sheila to dinner, too.
在你们的结婚纪念日里 她怎么能和其他人出去玩
How come she's going out with somebody else on your anniversary?
呃...
Well...
我让她去的
I told her to go.
你为什么要这么做?
Why'd you do that?
因为我想让你妈妈开心
Because I want your mother to be happy.
如果换作我 必须在家陪着病人
Well, if I had to stay at home and be with sick people
而有人却出去玩 我会生气的
while somebody else was out having fun, I'd be mad.
我没生气呀
Well, I'm not mad.
我会的
I would be.
也会很伤心
I'd be sad, too.
会因为她离开我而感到沮丧
Be kind of depressed because she left me.
- 是的... - 我会大哭 等等
- Yeah... - I'd be crying and everything.
我会很难过
Man, I'd be so upset.
- 好了 我们该... - 我没感到你在抑制自己
- You know, let's get... - I don't see how you hold it in.
来吧
Here you go.
坐好别动
Sit tight, don't move.
我过会儿回来
I'll be back.
嘿 Russo
Hey, Russo,
这孩子的事查清了
the kid's storry checks out.
看来你说的是真话
Looks like you were telling the truth.
你的老师证明了
Your teacher confirmed your story.
- 谢谢 - 没错
- Thank you. - Oh, yeah.
她还说了 你为你的同胞争了光
She also said to tell you you're a credit to your race.
我可以走了吗?
Can I leave now?
当然 等到你父母来接你
Sure-- soon as your parents come get you.
我父母?
My parents?
不能直接放我走吗? 我不能告诉妈妈我被捕了
Can't you just let me go? I can't tell my mom I got arrested.
告诉别人你卖的是赃物之前
Should have thought of that before you started
你应该考虑到这个问题
telling people you were selling stolen goods.
喂
Hello?
喂 爸爸
Hi, Dad.
Chris 你应该3点回家的 你现在在哪?
Chris, you're supposed to be home at 3:00. Where are you?
你...得到警察局来接我
I... need you to pick me up at the police station.
你被拘留了?!
You're in jail?!
无论你做了什么 一个字都别说
No matter what y did, don't say nothing.
- 但是 爸爸 我没有... - 我不是告诉你什么都别说吗?
- But, Dad, I didn't... - Didn't I tell you don't say nothing?
你所说的每一句话 将来都可能对你不利
Anything you say can and will be used against you.
我老爸的口吻像个律师似的
That  was as close as my father came to being a lawyer.
闭上你的嘴 我马上就到
Keep your mouth shut, I'll be there in a minute.
好的
Okay.
你卖这些东西是为了什么?
So what are you selling these things for, anyway?
全班去华盛顿特区野外郊游
A class trip to Washington, DC.
有花生酱口味或巧克力人的吗?
got any peanut butter Do-Si-Do?
只有这些了
Just these.
巧克力曲奇 哈?
Chocolate chip, huh?
多少钱?
How much are they?
警察们也是人
Say what you want about cops,
他们肯定也喜欢吃甜食
they sure got a mean sweet tooth.
在这签个名就可以走了
Sign right there and you're all set.
没事的 他们只是长了水痘
It's okay, they just got chicken pox.
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Dad.
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
你生我的气吗?
Are you mad at me?
当然 我快疯了
Yeah, I'm mad.
我没做错事 告诉他
I wasn't doing anything wrong. Tell him.
嘿 我可没说你没做错事
Hey, I never said you didn't do anything wrong.
你站在一个商店外面 说你那有赃物
You were standing outside a store claiming you had stolen goods.
这么做虽然不犯法 但也不对
It's not illegal, but it ain't right, either.
听你爸爸的话
You listen to your father.
他是个聪明人
He's a smart man.
谢谢
Thanks.
在NWA拳击开赛以前 你能一颗大牙不掉
Before NWA, you could actually leave a police station
大摇大摆的走出警察局
with the same amount of teeth you came in with.
爸爸?
Dad?
我还能去旅行吗?
Can I still go on the trip?
当然
Yeah. Come on.
当我梦想着能赶快出狱时
While I was dreaming about getting out of jail,
妈妈却在梦想着她是梦女郎
my mother was dreaming she was a Dreamgirl.
看谁回来了
Well. Look who's back.
演唱会怎么样?
How was the play?
宝贝 简直难以置信
Oh, baby, it was incredible!
你肯定会爱死它的
You would have loved it.
孩子们怎样了?
How are the kids?
Tonya睡着了
Well, Tonya's asleep,
Drew退烧了 还有 Chris被捕了
Drew's fever is down, and Chris got arrested.
但是...唯一重要的是你玩得很开心
But... the only thing that matters is that you had a good time.
什么? 你说Chris被捕了是什么意思?
What? What do you mean Chris got arrested?
已经解决了
It's over.
只是个误会
It was a misunderstanding.
我去接他了 也安顿好了这件事
I went down and took care of it.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
确定
Yeah.
你玩得开心吗?
Did you have a good time?
开心极了!
I had a great time!
宝贝 简直难以置信
Oh, baby, it was incredible.
太感谢你了...
Thank you so much...
你开心就好
Well, as long as you had a good time.
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
没什么
Nothing.
你有事
Something.
怎么了?
What?
在我们纪念日里 你一直Sheila在一块 就是这个事
What's wrong is you spent our anniversary with Sheila.
你怎么能丢下我去了?
How could you go without me?
宝贝 你让我去的
Baby, you told me to go.
我不是这个意思
I didn't mean it.
就像你告诉我不需要给你买礼物
It's just like when you tell me not to get you a gift.
我那样说 只是想说些好话
I was just saying that to be nice.
我不想浪费那票
I didn't want the tickets to go to waste.
我想让你去 让你玩得开心
And I wanted you to go and have a good time.
你竟然真照办了 我都快疯了
I'm just mad that you did.
你知道你在做没意义的事吗?
You know you're not making a bit of sense, right?
我知道
I know.
忘了它吧
Forget it.
座位怎么样?
How were the seats?
你不会想知道
You don't want to know.
那么好?
That good?
没错
Yup.
该死的Risky
Damn, Risky.
这是什么?
What's this?
我在回家的路上买的
I made a little stop on the way home.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
你给了我一张卡片
Oh, you got me a card.
Julius 你得打开它
Julius, just open the card.
尼克斯队决赛的票?!
Knicks playoff tickets?!
Risky说这是最好的座了
Risky said they're the best seats in the house.
太棒了!太棒了!
Oh! Yes! Yes!
- 怎么了? - 干得漂亮 Clyde!
- What happened? - That's right, Clyde!
干得漂亮 Clyde!
That's right, Clyde!
谢谢你 宝贝!
Thank you, baby!
啊 不
Uh-uh. No.
我们的纪念日还没结束呢
Our anniversary ain't over yet.
我说过那句话吗?
Ooh, did I say that?
我说了
I said it.
伙计 我等不及了!
Oh, man, I can't wait!
事实上 我们要去参观参议院!
We're actually going to visit the senate floor!
你知道吗 由于安全原因
Did you know, for security reasons
没有直接通往白宫的线路
there's no direct route to or from the White House?
以防有人试图杀害总统
Just in case somebody tries to kill the president?
他们该在Bed-Stuy做这事
They need to do that in Bed-Stuy.
嘿 讨厌鬼
Hey, cell nerd.
你脸颊上是什么?
What's that on your cheek?
看起来像水痘
It looks like chicken pox.